A Guide to the papers of Thomas C. Fichandler (1915-1997), Founding Executive Diector of the Arena Stage, 1950-2000
George Mason University Libraries
- Arena Stage: Thomas C. Fichandler files
  - Lease with RLA (folder 2 of 2), Folder 6 (Box Box 19)
  - Voter Trust Certificate, Foler 7 (Box Box 19)
  - Voting Trust Cerftificate 2, Folder 7 (Box Box 19)
  - Voting Trust Certificate 3, Folder 8 (Box Box 19)
  - Title Insurance for RLA Lease, Folder 9 (Box Box 19)
  - Fichandler - redevelopment land (1 of 2), Folder 10 (Box Box 19)
  - Fichandler - redevelopment land (2 of 2), Folder 11 (Box Box 19)
  - Contract of Sale / Warrentee Deed, Folder 12 (Box Box 19)
  - Agreement, Folder 13 (Box Box 19)
  - Blue Prints, Folder 1 (Box Box 20)
  - Fire Coder, Folder 2 (Box Box 20)
  - Letters for the layout of building, Folder 3 (Box Box 20)
  - Plans of Development, Folder 4 (Box Box 20)
  - Arena II - Subcontractors and Drawing of Layout, Folder 5 (Box Box 20)
  - Mechanical Specific Proposals and Blueprints, Folder 6 (Box Box 20)
  - Release of Liens, Arena II, Folder 7 (Box Box 20)
  - Stage Safety / Protection, Folder 8 (Box Box 20)
  - useof the theatre manual, Folder 1 (Box Box 21)
  - Visionaisc Corp. 1976-77, Folder 2 (Box Box 21)
  - Volunteer Organization 1980, Folder 3 (Box Box 21)
  - Wage Freeze 1971, Folder 4 (Box Box 21)
  - Washington Performing Arts Society, Folder 5 (Box Box 21)
  - Waterfront Washington Association, Folder 6 (Box Box 21)
  - Water Service Repair, Folder 7 (Box Box 21)
  - LORT correspondence1974, Folder 8 (Box Box 21)
  - LORT correspondence 1974, Folder 9 (Box Box 21)
  - WYCB, Folder 10 (Box Box 21)
  - Statements before joint hearing 3/72, Folder 11 (Box Box 21)
  - Royalty Committee Report 8/73, Folder 12 (Box Box 21)
  - LORT agreement Sept. 1978, Folder 13 (Box Box 21)
  - LORT correspondence 1975, Folder 14 (Box Box 21)
  - LORT correspondence 1975, Folder 15 (Box Box 21)
  - LORT Correspondence 1975, Folder 16 (Box Box 21)
  - LORT correspondence 1976, Folder 17 (Box Box 21)
  - LORT correspondence 1978, Folder 18 (Box Box 21)
  - LORT Correspondence 1979, Folder 19 (Box Box 21)
  - LORT membership, Folder 20 (Box Box 21)
  - LORT arbitration, Folder 21 (Box Box 21)
  - Brademas Committee Statement, Folder 22 (Box Box 21)
  - LORT meeting information, Folder 23 (Box Box 21)
  - LORT agreement 1966, Folder 24 (Box Box 21)
  - LORT agreement 1973, Folder 25 (Box Box 21)
  - LORT minutes, Folder 26 (Box Box 21)
  - AEA correspondence 1974-1980, Folder 27 (Box Box 21)
  - AEA correspondence 1974-1980, Folder 28 (Box Box 21)
  - LORT correspondence 1982-1983, Folder 29 (Box Box 21)
  - Survey of theater size and potential income, Folder 30 (Box Box 21)
  - LORT correspondence 1977, Folder 31 (Box Box 21)
  - "Dream Engine" production material, Folder 1 (Box Box 22)
  - "Dream Engine" Correspondence, Folder 2 (Box Box 22)
  - "Dream Engine" producation contracts, Folder 3 (Box Box 22)
  - "Dream Engine" direction contract for Dick Pearlman, Folder 4 (Box Box 22)
  - "Dream Engine", staging techniques producers primer, Folder 5 (Box Box 22)
  - "Dream Engine", Personnel files, Folder 6 (Box Box 22)
  - "The Last Analysis" producation materials, Folder 7 (Box Box 22)
  - Production material for misc. plays, 1970 - 1971 season, Folder 8 (Box Box 22)
  - "The Sign in Sidney Brustein's Window" production material, Folder 9 (Box Box 22)
  - "What the Butler Saw", production material, Folder 10 (Box Box 22)
  - "Pueblo", production material, Folder 11 (Box Box 22)
  - "Awahe and Sing", production material, Folder 12 (Box Box 22)
  - "Wipe-Out Games", production material, Folder 13 (Box Box 22)
  - "The Ruling Class", production material, Folder 14 (Box Box 22)
  - "Mother Courage", production material, Folder 15 (Box Box 22)
  - "The Night Thoreau Spent in Jail", production material, Folder 16 (Box Box 22)
  - Misc. production material, 1971 - 1972 season, Folder 17 (Box Box 22)
  - "Tricks", production material, Folder 18 (Box Box 22)
  - "Status Quo Vadis", production material, Folder 19 (Box Box 22)
  - "Uptight", production material, Folder 20 (Box Box 22)
  - "Conflict of Interest", production material, Folder 21 (Box Box 22)
  - "The House of Blue Leaves", production material, Folder 22 (Box Box 22)
  - "Twelfth Night", production material, Folder 23 (Box Box 22)
  - "Moon Children", production material, Folder 24 (Box Box 22)
  - "Moon Childeren", "Investors", production material, Folder 25 (Box Box 22)
  - "Pantagleize:, production material, Folder 26 (Box Box 22)
  - ""Rasin", production material (1 of 2), Folder 27 (Box Box 22)
  - "Rasin", production material (2 of 2), Folder 28 (Box Box 22)
  - seasonal contracts, 1972-1973, Folder 29 (Box Box 22)
  - The Paper Bag Players, 1972 - 1973, Folder 30 (Box Box 22)
  - "The Basic Training of Pavlo H.", production material, Folder 31 (Box Box 22)
  - "The Little Theatre of the Deaf", production material, Folder 32 (Box Box 22)
  - "The New Theatre", production material, Folder 33 (Box Box 22)
  - "One Flew Over the Cuchoo's Nest", production material, Folder 34 (Box Box 22)
  - "Enemies", production material, Folder 35 (Box Box 22)
  - "A Look at the Fiftes", production material, Folder 36 (Box Box 22)
  - "Scheinschmitt", production material, Folder 37 (Box Box 22)
  - "A Public Prosecutor is Sick", production material, Folder 35 (Box Box 22)
  - "Our Town", production material, Folder 39 (Box Box 22)
  - "The Foursome", production material, Folder 40 (Box Box 22)
  - "The Hostage", production material, Folder 41 (Box Box 22)
  - "I am a woman", production material, Folder 42 (Box Box 22)
  - "Horatio", production material, Folder 43 (Box Box 22)
  - "Relatively Speaking", production material, Folder 44 (Box Box 22)
  - "Maddness of God", prodcution material, Folder 45 (Box Box 22)
  - AEA negotiations, Folder 1 (Box Box 23)
  - LORT correspondence 1980 - 1981, Folder 2 (Box Box 23)
  - LORT meeting minutes, Folder 3 (Box Box 23)
  - Living Stage, Folder 4 (Box Box 23)
  - LORT meeting minutes, Folder 5 (Box Box 23)
  - Council on Foundations, Folder 6 (Box Box 23)
  - Cultural Alliance (1 of 2), Folder 7 (Box Box 23)
  - Cultural Alliance (2 of 2), Folder 9 (Box Box 23)
  - Cultural Alliance, Folder 10 (Box Box 23)
  - Cultural Alliance, Folder 11 (Box Box 23)
  - D.C. Black Rep. Company, Folder 12 (Box Box 23)
  - D.C. Council, Folder 13 (Box Box 23)
  - Film Festival 1964 - 1965, Accounting, Folder 14 (Box Box 23)
  - Film Festival 1964 - 1965, correspondence, Folder 15 (Box Box 23)
  - Film Festival 1964-1965, correspondence, Folder 16 (Box Box 23)
  - 42nd street project, Folder 17 (Box Box 23)
  - Jean Frost, Memorial Gifts, Folder 18 (Box Box 23)
  - Arena Stage Guild, Folder 19 (Box Box 23)
  - Arlington County Cultural Center internship program, Folder 20 (Box Box 23)
  - American University internship programs, Folder 21 (Box Box 23)
  - Internship Program, Folder 22 (Box Box 23)
  - General Internship program, Folder 24 (Box Box 23)
  - George Washington University, internship program, Folder 25 (Box Box 23)
  - Production interns 1967-1969, Folder 26 (Box Box 23)
  - Writer's Workshop internship program, Folder 27 (Box Box 23)
  - Work Study intern program 1973-1974, Folder 28 (Box Box 23)
  - Work Study intern program 1971-1972, Folder 29 (Box Box 23)
  - Downtown box office proposal, Folder 1 (Box Box 24)
  - Price Sale 1977 - 1978 (Box Office), Folder 2 (Box Box 24)
  - Box Office: 1975 proposal, Folder 3 (Box Box 24)
  - Box Office: price scales presant and proposed, July 1969, Folder 4 (Box Box 24)
  - Box Office:attendence and income, 1961 - 1971, Folder 5 (Box Box 24)
  - Box Office: subscription chart 1957 - 1969, Folder 6 (Box Box 24)
  - Box Office: study 1980, Folder 7 (Box Box 24)
  - Box Office: income, 1984-1985 season, Folder 8 (Box Box 24)
  - Box Office: income, 1982-1983 season, Folder 9 (Box Box 24)
  - Box Office: income, 1981-1982 season, Folder 10 (Box Box 24)
  - Box Office: income 1980-1981 season, Folder 11 (Box Box 24)
  - Box Office: proposed prices, 1983-1984 season, Folder 12 (Box Box 24)
  - Box Office:1983-1984 season, Folder 13 (Box Box 24)
  - subscription history 1961 - present, Folder 14 (Box Box 24)
  - Box Office: Ticket Prices, 1986-1987 season, Folder 15 (Box Box 24)
  - Box Office: Ticket prices, 1985-1986 season, Folder 16 (Box Box 24)
  - Box Office: Subscriptions and prices, 1984-1985 season, Folder 17 (Box Box 24)
  - Box Office: Subscriptions 1982, AD copy, Folder 18 (Box Box 24)
  - Box Office: Subscriptions, 1982-1983 season, Folder 19 (Box Box 24)
  - Box Office: subscriptions, 1982-1983 custom letters, Folder 20 (Box Box 24)
  - airplane noise problems, Folder 21 (Box Box 24)
  - Letters to Politicians, Folder 22 (Box Box 24)
  - Population growth and income, Folder 23 (Box Box 24)
  - IRS Federal unemployment and tax recovery payments 1964-1965, Folder 24 (Box Box 24)
  - public foundation forms, Folder 25 (Box Box 24)
  - IRS federal tax exemptions 1960, Folder 26 (Box Box 24)
  - Postage information, Folder 27 (Box Box 24)
  - Press, Folder 28 (Box Box 24)
  - production meeting minutes, Folder 29 (Box Box 24)
  - programs, Folder 30 (Box Box 24)
  - public relataions progress report, Folder 31 (Box Box 24)
  - Richmond Bill, H.R. 1042 (96th Congress, 1st session), Folder 32 (Box Box 24)
  - Rotating Repertory report / sales tax, Folder 33 (Box Box 24)
  - season schedules and seating plans, Folder 34 (Box Box 24)
  - Screen Scope/ WETA, Folder 35 (Box Box 24)
  - Sound System / Southeastern Theatre conference, Folder 36 (Box Box 24)
  - Thomas Finhandler speeches, Folder 37 (Box Box 24)
  - Spring Hill Conference, Jan. 5-7, 1974, Folder 38 (Box Box 24)
  - Spring Hill Conference, Jan. 16 and 17, 1975, Folder 39 (Box Box 24)
  - Administrative Staff Meetings, 1984-1985, Folder 40 (Box Box 24)
  - Administrative Staff meetings 1983, Folder 41 (Box Box 24)
  - Staff meetings 1980-1981, Folder 42 (Box Box 24)
  - Staff meetings 1979-1980, Folder 43 (Box Box 24)
  - Staff meeting 1978-1979, Folder 44 (Box Box 24)
  - weekly Friday meetings minutes, 1977-1978, Folder 1 (Box Box 25)
  - mini staff meetings 1975-1976, Folder 2 (Box Box 25)
  - administrative staff meeting, May 1981 - Dec. 1982, Folder 3 (Box Box 25)
  - mini staff meeting minutes, 1974-1975, Folder 4 (Box Box 25)
  - staff meeting minutes 1974-1975, Folder 5 (Box Box 25)
  - staff meeting minutes, 1973-1974, Folder 6 (Box Box 25)
  - mini staff meeting minutes, Folder 7 (Box Box 25)
  - staff meeting minutes 1972-1973, Folder 8 (Box Box 25)
  - staff meeting minutes 1970-1971, Folder 9 (Box Box 25)
  - staff meeting minutes, 1969-1970, Folder 10 (Box Box 25)
  - staff meeting minutes, 1968-1969, Folder 11 (Box Box 25)
  - staff meeting minutes, 1967-1968, Folder 12 (Box Box 25)
  - staff meeting minutes, 1966-1967, Folder 13 (Box Box 25)
  - staff meetings 1965-1966, Folder 14 (Box Box 25)
  - staff meetings, 1964-1965, Folder 15 (Box Box 25)
  - American Council for the Arts (1 of 3), Folder 16 (Box Box 25)
  - American Council for the Arts (2 of 3), Folder 17 (Box Box 25)
  - American Council for the Arts (3 of 3), Folder 18 (Box Box 25)
  - Arts Management bulletins, Folder 19 (Box Box 25)
  - Arts Administration, Folder 20 (Box Box 25)
  - American Playwrites Theatre, Folder 21 (Box Box 25)
  - Applied Management Sciences, Folder 22 (Box Box 25)
  - ANTA, Folder 23 (Box Box 25)
  - 1973-1979 dinner benefits, Folder 24 (Box Box 25)
  - Annual narrative Report 71-72, Folder 25 (Box Box 25)
  - Accolades, Folder 26 (Box Box 25)
  - Accounting, Folder 27 (Box Box 25)
  - Ad Hoc Cultural Resources group, Folder 28 (Box Box 25)
  - Administrative study, Folder 29 (Box Box 25)
  - AFTA, Folder 30 (Box Box 25)
  - AFT, Folder 31 (Box Box 25)
  - Arena Angels, Folder 32 (Box Box 25)
  - AEA, Folder 33 (Box Box 25)
  - AEA, Folder 34 (Box Box 25)
  - AEA negotiations 1975-1979, Folder 35 (Box Box 25)
  - AEA correspondence 1969-1973, Folder 1 (Box Box 26)
  - AEA Correspondence 1960-1973, Folder 2 (Box Box 26)
  - AEA correspondence 1960-1973, Folder 3 (Box Box 26)
  - ticket prices survey, Folder 4 (Box Box 26)
  - negotiations 1966-1972, Folder 5 (Box Box 26)
  - Negotiations 1966-1972, Folder 6 (Box Box 26)
  - negotiations 1966-1972, Folder 7 (Box Box 26)
  - Touring, Folder 8 (Box Box 26)
  - Touring, Folder 9 (Box Box 26)
  - United Arts Organization, Folder 10 (Box Box 26)
  - United Arts Organization, Folder 11 (Box Box 26)
  - US international cultural trade center proposal 1983, Folder 12 (Box Box 26)
  - United Scenic Artists, Folder 13 (Box Box 26)
  - Letters to the Editor, Folder 14 (Box Box 26)
  - Lighting board, Folder 15 (Box Box 26)
  - Baltimore Incident: living stage, Folder 16 (Box Box 26)
  - Conservatory Proposal, Folder 17 (Box Box 26)
  - Granite Gallery Incident, Folder 18 (Box Box 26)
  - Living Stage: General, Folder 19 (Box Box 26)
  - analysis of expenses and income, Folder 20 (Box Box 26)
  - Living Stage: General, Folder 21 (Box Box 26)
  - AEA 1980, Folder 22 (Box Box 26)
  - URTA, 1972-1974, Folder 23 (Box Box 26)
  - Public Interest Public Relations, Folder 1 (Box Box 27)
  - Public Interest Public Relations, Folder 2 (Box Box 27)
  - Board of Education, Folder 3 (Box Box 27)
  - energy crisis, Folder 4 (Box Box 27)
  - european Summer Theatre, Folder 5 (Box Box 27)
  - Events, Folder 6 (Box Box 27)
  - DC Fiscal Affairs (1 of 2), Folder 7 (Box Box 27)
  - DC Fiscal Affairs (2 of 2), Folder 8 (Box Box 27)
  - FACT (1 of 2), Folder 9 (Box Box 27)
  - FACT (2 of 2), Folder 10 (Box Box 27)
  - FEDAPT, Folder 11 (Box Box 27)
  - Indians, New York Co., Folder 12 (Box Box 27)
  - House Management, Folder 13 (Box Box 27)
  - Honeywell, Folder 14 (Box Box 27)
  - Hogates, Folder 15 (Box Box 27)
  - Hawthorne School, Folder 16 (Box Box 27)
  - GWETA, Folder 17 (Box Box 27)
  - Guthrie Theatre, Folder 18 (Box Box 27)
  - Tintypes Touring, Folder 19 (Box Box 27)
  - 1979-1980 season, general information, Folder 20 (Box Box 27)
  - 1980-1981 season general info., Folder 21 (Box Box 27)
  - 1980-1981 season, general info., Folder 22 (Box Box 27)
  - Executive Director, Folder 23 (Box Box 27)
  - General Contractor letters, Edward M. Crouch, Folder 1 (Box Box 28)
  - Hartford Insurance Company, Folder 2 (Box Box 27)
  - Carroll Seating Company, Folder 3 (Box Box 28)
  - Arena II seating, Folder 4 (Box Box 28)
  - Specifications Book for Arena II, individual bound book (Box Box 28)
  - Edward Crouch, contractor files, Folder 1 (Box Box 29)
  - Harry Weese and Associates, building designs, Folder 2 (Box Box 29)
  - Building problems, Folder 3 (Box Box 29)
  - Ideas, Folder 4 (Box Box 29)
  - Foundation Permit, Folder 5 (Box Box 29)
  - NCPC and District Commissioning correspondence, Folder 6 (Box Box 29)
  - Plans Approval, Folder 7 (Box Box 29)
  - Test Reports, Folder 8 (Box Box 29)
  - Morton, Thomas and Associates, Folder 9 (Box Box 29)
  - Venetian Blinds, Folder 10 (Box Box 29)
  - Section 15 and Urban Renewal, Folder 11 (Box Box 29)
  - Blue Prints for Arena II, Folder 12 (Box Box 29)
  - Arena Enterprises Board Minutes May, 1955 - June 1959, Folder 1 (Box Box 30)
  - Board of Trustees minutes 1959-1961, Folder 2 (Box Box 30)
  - Board of trustees Minutes 1962-1964, Folder 3 (Box Box 30)
  - Board Minutes 1965-1979, Folder 4 (Box Box 30)
  - Board Minutes 1965-1979, Folder 5 (Box Box 30)
  - Board Minutes 1965-1979, Folder 6 (Box Box 30)
  - Board Minutes 1965-1979, Folder 7 (Box Box 30)
  - old board list 8/83, Folder 1 (Box Box 31)
  - Board of Trustees files 1980-1984, Folder 2 (Box Box 31)
  - Board of Trustees files 1985-1987, Folder 3 (Box Box 31)
  - Executive Committee Minutes april 1981- Jan. 1987, Folder 4 (Box Box 31)
  - Captial Arts Communication, Folder 1 (Box Box 32)
  - Capital Arts Communication, Folder 2 (Box Box 32)
  - Capital/budget, Folder 3 (Box Box 32)
  - Federal tax exemption, Folder 4 (Box Box 32)
  - Certificate of good standing, Folder 5 (Box Box 32)
  - DC tax exemption form, Folder 6 (Box Box 32)
  - Certification of incorporation, Folder 7 (Box Box 32)
  - Combustioneer, Folder 8 (Box Box 32)
  - Communication Committee 1983, Folder 9 (Box Box 32)
  - William Stewart correspondence answered 1986-1987, Folder 10 (Box Box 32)
  - Colorado 1986, Folder 11 (Box Box 32)
  - Development 1978-1980, Folder 1 (Box Box 33)
  - Development 1985-1986, Folder 2 (Box Box 33)
  - DC Commission on the Arts, general correspondence, Folder 3 (Box Box 33)
  - DC Commission: Special, Folder 4 (Box Box 33)
  - Marion Barry, Folder 5 (Box Box 33)
  - DC Commsiion on the Arts and Humanities 1981-1982, Folder 6 (Box Box 33)
  - DC liquor license, Folder 7 (Box Box 33)
  - DC Achohal Beverage Control, Folder 8 (Box Box 33)
  - liquor license correspondence, Folder 1 (Box Box 34)
  - Lease Agreement - DC Arena, Folder 2 (Box Box 34)
  - Equity/LORT negotiations 1984-1986, Folder 3 (Box Box 34)
  - Executive Committee 1983/84 and 1984/85, Folder 4 (Box Box 34)
  - Carousel budget, Folder 5 (Box Box 34)
  - Executive Committee 1985/86, Folder 6 (Box Box 34)
  - Executive Committe Minutes 1985/86, Folder 1 (Box Box 35)
  - Executive Committee Minutes1986/87, Folder 2 (Box Box 35)
  - Executive Committee Minutes 12/86, Folder 3 (Box Box 35)
  - Executive Committee minutes 1/87 (audio tape), Folder 4 (Box Box 35)
  - Executive Committee meeting 1/1987, Folder 5 (Box Box 35)
  - Executive Committee 2/1987, Folder 6 (Box Box 35)
  - Executive Committee meeting 3/1987 (audio cassette), Folder 7 (Box Box 35)
  - Executive Committee Meeting 3/1987, Folder 8 (Box Box 35)
  - Executive Committee meeting 4/1987, Folder 9 (Box Box 35)
  - Executive Committee 5/1987 (audio), Folder 10 (Box Box 35)
  - Executive Committee meeting 5/1987, Folder 11 (Box Box 35)
  - Executive Committee Minutes 1987/1988, Folder 12 (Box Box 35)
  - Executive Committee meeting 7/1987, Folder 13 (Box Box 35)
  - Executive Committee Meeting 7/1987, Folder 14 (Box Box 35)
  - Executive Committee 11/1987, Folder 15 (Box Box 35)
  - 1964 annual sustaining fund drive, folder 1 (Box box 36)
  - D.C. admissions sales tax (1 of 2), folder 2 (Box box 36)
  - D.C. admissions sales tax (2 of 2), folder 3 (Box box 36)
  - standing room variance, 1980, folder 4 (Box box 36)
  - student matinees, folder 5 (Box box 36)
  - subscription drive; 1981-1982, folder 6 (Box box 36)
  - summer acting workshop, folder 7 (Box box 36)
  - D.C. gross receipts - tax, folder 8 (Box box 36)
  - annual sustaining fund drive (1 of 2), folder 8 (Box box 36)
  - annual sustaining fund drive (2 of 2), folder 9 (Box box 36)
  - economic studies of theatres, folder 1 (Box box 37)
  - experimental theatre, folder 2 (Box box 37)
  - financial budget 1980-1981, folder 3 (Box box 37)
  - financial budget 1981-1982, folder 4 (Box box 37)
  - financial budget 1982-1983, folder 5 (Box box 37)
  - financial budget 1983-1984, folder 6 (Box box 37)
  - financial budget 1984-1985, folder 7 (Box box 37)
  - National Corporate Theatre Fund Inc. 1977-1979, folder 1 (Box box 38)
  - National Corporate Theatre Fund Inc. 1977-1979, folder 2 (Box box 38)
  - National Corporate Theatre Fund Inc. 1980-1981, folder 3 (Box box 38)
  - National Corporate Theatre Fund Inc. 1980-1981, folder 4 (Box box 38)
  - Trustees 1987-1988, folder 1 (Box box 39)
  - memo to Elspeth from Josh, April 13, 1988, folder 2 (Box box 39)
  - nominating and evaluation 1985-1987, folder 3 (Box box 39)
  - Rogers and Cowan 1986, folder 4 (Box box 39)
  - Rogers and Cowan, 1987, folder 5 (Box box 39)
  - redevelopment land agency, folder 6 (Box box 39)
  - reserve policy/investment, folder 7 (Box box 39)
  - Riverfest 1987-1989, folder 8 (Box box 39)
  - Russian Tour, 1973, folder 9 (Box box 39)
  - Russian Tour 1973, folder 10 (Box box 39)
  - Russian Tour 1973, folder 11 (Box box 39)
  - Russian Tour 1973, folder 12 (Box box 39)
  - Russian Tour 1973, folder 13 (Box box 39)
  - Russian Tour 1973, folder 14 (Box box 39)
  - J.J. Pickle 1973, folder 15 (Box box 39)
  - Russian Tour 1973, folder 16 (Box box 39)
  - Russian Tour 1973, folder 17 (Box box 39)
  - Russian Tour 1973, folder 18 (Box box 39)
  - quotables 1970's, folder 19 (Box box 39)
  - senior staff meeting minutes 1989-1991, folder 20 (Box box 39)
  - postal information, folder 21 (Box box 39)
  - protective entity, folder 22 (Box box 39)
  - senior staff meeting minutes 1988-1989, folder 23 (Box box 39)
  - staff retreat 1985, folder 24 (Box box 39)
  - pension plans - other theaters, folder 1 (Box box 40)
  - "over-the-top"committee minutes 1969, folder 2 (Box box 40)
  - stage II plaque orders, folder 3 (Box box 40)
  - pension plan, quips and quotes, folder 4 (Box box 40)
  - pension plan information, folder 5 (Box box 40)
  - originals nominating evaluating 1984-1986, folder 6 (Box box 40)
  - nominating and evaluating, folder 7 (Box box 40)
  - new plays series 1983, folder 8 (Box box 40)
  - operations committee 1979-1983, folder 9 (Box box 40)
  - opportuniyt resources for the arts, Inc., folder 10 (Box box 40)
  - Ad Hoc Committee 1985, folder 11 (Box box 40)
  - nomination and evaluation committee 1981-1986, folder 12 (Box box 40)
  - nominating and evaluating handout 1985, folder 13 (Box box 40)
  - trustees committee, 1989, folder 14 (Box box 40)
  - nominating and evaluation committee, 1986-1987, folder 15 (Box box 40)
  - general correspondence, folder 1 (Box box 41)
  - general correspondence, folder 2 (Box box 41)
  - financial correspondence, folder 3 (Box box 41)
  - director contracts, folder 4 (Box box 41)
  - misc. materials, folder 5 (Box box 41)
  - Samuel French Inc. 1978, folder 6 (Box box 41)
  - "Starting here, Starting now", folder 7 (Box box 41)
  - "Lower Depths", correspondence, folder 8 (Box box 41)
  - Fichandler materials, folder 9 (Box box 41)
  - economic data, folder 10 (Box box 42)
  - operation analysis spread sheet 1962-1969, folder 2 (Box box 42)
  - 5 year budget projections late 70's through early 80's, folder 3 (Box box 42)
  - NASA proposal for "Star-Track" lighting unit, folder 4 (Box box 42)
  - musicians, folder 5 (Box box 42)
  - correspondence: Pear Henry E., folder 6 (Box box 42)
  - partnership for the arts, folder 7 (Box box 42)
  - parking situation, folder 8 (Box box 42)
  - correspondence: Joseph Papp, folder 9 (Box box 42)
  - Opera America, Inc., folder 10 (Box box 42)
  - office controls, folder 11 (Box box 42)
  - management, folder 12 (Box box 42)
  - The New National Theatre, folder 13 (Box box 42)
  - New Dramaists, folder 14 (Box box 42)
  - National Theatre - Papp Proposal 1971-1972, folder 15 (Box box 42)
  - National Theatre, folder 16 (Box box 42)
  - National Research Cneter of the Arts, Inc., folder 17 (Box box 42)
  - budget production 1964-1969, folder 18 (Box box 42)
  - budgets production 1967-1968, folder 19 (Box box 42)
  - executive committee meeting minutes, misc. folders (Box box 43)